我们没有很长的时间 但是我很想  如果可能的话
We don't have very long, but what I'd like to do, in an ideal world...
接着写那首"爱情解剖"
...is continue the "Autopsy" song.
但是我担心要从这首歌改成
But I think it's gonna be very hard to get back from there...
科拉要的那首"重新找到爱" 可不是很容易
...into "Way Back Into Love," which is the title that Cora demands.
我们要做就是接着做格雷格的 那个"天使之死"
What we could do is continue with Greg "the Angel of Death's" version.
那是抄袭
That's plagiarism.
是吧  说的对  就是这样
Yes. Yes, yes. Good. Excellent.
我是不会剽窃别人的作品的
I would never in a million years use someone else's work.
很高兴你同意我的看法
I'm very glad you agree.
那么  我们需要什么呢 我们要作一首全新的曲子
So, what we need, we need something brand-new.
-那我们讨论一下  给科拉写的歌  -是的
- So let's see. A song for Cora.  - Yes.